Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching.
This time, we have a special interview with Morning Musume。 This time, I'll be talking with Ayumi Ishida of Morning Musume。 23's Ayumi Ishida and
and Ayumi Kudo of Chuchusu.
These two will be our guests this time, so please bear with us until the end.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Now that August has arrived
It really feels like summer is in full swing.
The hot days are continuing day after day.
Let's take care of ourselves and do our best!
Project 2023 Summer City Circuit is now being held.
Yes, Morning Musume。 23 was scheduled to perform in Miyagi Prefecture, my hometown, on August 5.
This is the first time to perform in my hometown since I became able to speak out.
Wow, it's going to be fun!
So I'm really looking forward to hearing my fans' reactions when I say "I'm home" for the first time in a while.
I'm really looking forward to hearing the reactions of my fans when I say "I'm home" for the first time in a while.
On the night of August 5th, the Sendai Tanabata Festival will be held on the 6th, 7th and 8th.
There will be fireworks on the eve of the festival, right?
I'm really looking forward to it!
So I'm looking forward to the excitement in Miyagi Prefecture as a whole!
Wow, it's wonderful!
The next Juice Juice concert will be on August 6th, and it will be my first time to perform at the exquisite Shinjuku.
It will be my first time!
I often have trouble finding the vending machines at a new venue.
I also wonder how long I can stretch my arms when I'm standing in a row.
the size of the stage.
I make sure to check everything carefully and hope to make it a wonderful time.
In addition, Morning Musume。 23 will be performing on August 30.
Morning Musume。 Best Selection THE 25th Anniversary will be released on August 30.
This new album is a re-recording of songs from the past by the current members,
We are very excited about the completion of this album, and we are looking forward to the release,
We are very excited about this new album, so please look forward to it.
I am looking forward to it.
Please take a look at this video.
Here it is!
Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow!Wow Wow Wow Wow
Summer Challenger
Wow Wow Yeah
Wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow
Honestly, it's hot. I want to go home.
Everybody's dressed up but I'm not freaked out here
Complex, happy, happy
Look, I'm more mature than I used to be
I'm a gem in the rough. I'm a family man.
I'm not even buried yet, and by now you're already looking at me like I'm happy.
You're good at giving me a hard time.
You've got to do better than that.
I'll be brave. Now, now, now.
Now, now, now!
I cried again this year
I can't let go of my weak heart
I want to be free
Summer Channel Now
Summer Challenger
Wow Wow Yeah
Someday it'll be too late
It's not like I'm a kid
I don't care. I'm not a kid.
I'm just saying... I cracked it.
I have to play. Like me.
Give it back to him. He'll feel better.
I don't need your advice.
I don't need comfort. I don't need advice.
I know especially. Everything, everything, everything.
I'll meet someone who'll smile and hug me.
I'm meeting someone tonight
Summer Challenger
Checas and snubs
I won't jump ahead of you
So don't let me fool you
I'm coming.I'm going.
I don't need comfort.
I don't need more advice.
I know what I'm doing.
Everything. Everything. Everything.
I'll never give up my smile
I'll meet someone who'll hold me
Tonight I'm gonna meet someone who's gonna hold me
Summer Challenge Unleashed
Summer Challenge
Wow Wow Wow Wow
Summer Challenger
Wow Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah
ON! véhicLE
Let's work together!
Morning Musume。 23's Ayumi Ishida and Juice- Juice's Ayumi Kudo will be presenting the "Halo! STE!
From here, I would like to ask you a few questions about each other.
First of all, I'm going to ask you some questions, so you don't have to think too much and answer them quickly.
Let's begin.
Tell us about your recent episode of octopus love.
I am addicted to agar octopus.
Fiesta Fiesta was released 6 years ago in August.
It's a song that really gets me fired up and into high gear, so much so that I think of it when I think of live performances.
Ayumi Kudo will turn 19 next month.
What do you want to do while you are still 18?
To go to a cake buffet.
What is your favorite job as an idol?
Of course I am a live performer, but I also go to Suzukka as an octopus, and I am also a regular contributor to the monthly magazine "Carlife.
Hello Project is celebrating its 25th anniversary this year. Which of the past songs would you like to wear at least once in your career?
I would like to wear the pink costume of "Bare and Facing Each Other. And I want to dance to that song.
I want to bare myself. I see. Thank you very much.
I'm sorry. It's called "Octopus Agar Dako," which is an agar that is addicted to octopus. The name is based on the image of the agar you may have imagined, but it is an octopus from the deep sea.
It goes to the deep sea. I am not talking about food.
It is alive. There is a type of octopus called the agar octopus, which is said to have seven arms. Normally, octopuses have eight arms.It is alive. There is a type of octopus called the agar octopus, which is said to have seven arms. Normally, octopuses have eight arms.
But it turns into a squid, doesn't it?
That's right. It has 10 arms.
I'm sorry.
But in fact, it has eight arms, and the other arm is said to be located under the eye, which is a little difficult to see.
I thought it was cute.
I thought it was interesting.
I am interested in it. I am interested in it.
I see. And your love of octopuses has led to your work.
I am very happy to be in Shizuoka and learn about octopus ecology through a magazine called "Likeable Color".
I guess it's true. It makes you happy when your love leads to work, doesn't it?
I am very happy. I will work very hard.
I see. Thank you very much.
Questions for Ms. Ishida will come after the VTR.
Hallo! STE.
CHOOSE CHOOSE Pride Bright NOW ON SALE
CHOOSE CHOOSE Funky Flossing NOW ON SALE
Ocha no Obaba! New Single
A little emotional instability! Summer! Now on sale!
Auntie of Tea! New Single
Tea lady! Mahalo ba! Ikaenova!
Showa and 2021 Wachamacha! Now on sale!
Shaken na!
The Power of Believing Badly
Ordinary but forbidding Nara
Tea lady! New Single
Shaken na! Ale! Now on sale!
so many to choose from
I can't choose just one!
Absolute Tokimeijer!
Pampaka-pan all over the world! Before that
Tea Auntie! New Single
More Torimidori now on sale!
Hallo! STE!
Next, I would like to ask a question to Mr. Ishida. Please give me your best regards.
Ms. Ishida says that she posts pictures of curry on Instagram. What kind of curry do you want to eat now?Mr. Ishida posts pictures of his curry on Instagram. What kind of curry do you want to eat now?
Shabashabu Japanese-style curry!
What is the key to today's hair arrangement?
Yes, I used something that seems to be popular.
It will be 12 years since I joined Morning Musume。 Next month will mark the 12th anniversary since joining Morning Musume。 Looking back on this period, what has been your strongest weapon?
My dance.
When you were asked to be cool for a photo shoot, what should I do with my facial expression and pose?
Yes, like this.
This is what I learned.
Which song in the history of Hello! Project would you choose as a cool song to dance to?
Romain My Lia Boy.
Thank you very much.
Well, I was really worried about my expression and pose when I was asked to be cool in the photo shoot,
I was wondering if I could ask you about it today.
I think it would be better to have one of the angles facing the viewer in a nuanced way,
I want to have my hand somewhere, so if I use one hand, my left hand is not very good.
I'm not good at it.
That's right.
That's why I put both hands on it.
I was wondering where my left hand was. I was wondering where my left hand was going.
I usually hold the microphone, so I wondered what I should do.
I neglected it.
That's right. I'm still not very good at it.
I'm going to use it.
I understand. Thank you very much. I am saved.
I'm glad. I'm looking forward to it. From now on.
Yes, I will do my best.
Cool picture of Yume.
I look forward to working with you.
Yes, I'm looking forward to it.
May I ask you what you think is cool about the song?
The music of this song is cool to begin with, so I thought I would think it as a cool song based on the image of the music,
But looking at the choreography alone, I think it is very easy to deliver power to the audience,
If you ask me if I am doing very difficult steps, it's not like that,
But I can hear the sound of the chorus before the chorus, and I can feel the energy of the chorus,I was very happy to hear the sound of the choreography before the chorus, for example,
I think it is a choreography that can easily incorporate each person's individuality,
There are official dance shots of Romain on YouTube.
So when I saw them, I could see that they were all dancing by themselves,
It was cool to see the individuality of each dancer,
When we usually perform this song live, how can we make the strength of the song come across in the choreography?
When we usually perform this song live, we have to think about how we can put the strength in the choreography,
I think it's cool that it's not just dance.
Yes, it was cool. I am glad to hear it from so close. Thank you very much.
Hallo! Stay tuned for more after this!
This is Natsuyaki Masashi.
This is Minami Okamura from Beyonce.
I'll do my best to make sure it's delicious.
So, what shall we make now?
Today, I'm going to make...what?
Cheese crepes.
It's hard to say, isn't it?
What is it?
It's Indian, isn't it?
Oh, no!
It's getting slippery.
What would you like to start with this time?
Yes, I would like to make the ingredients for the naandok first.
I would like to make the ingredients for the naandok first.
I would like to slice tomatoes.
Let's cut them.
Yes, yes. Lastly, let's cut the tomatoes.
Let's turn it this way.
Let's show the cross section.
Maybe a little thinner.
It doesn't have to be too thin.
Pounding.
Boil the sausage... boil?
Boil.
Boil?
Boil-o.Boylu.
A little gal.
Boilou.
I think it's okay if just Boyle turns it off and doesn't burn it.
About 2 minutes with this.
2 minutes.
Yes, boil it.
Crispy, and then finally, it's like this.
It's like popping out, isn't it?
Juicy.
Juicy. Yes, yes.
To do that, the skin must not break.
When you bake it, the skin breaks.
It's difficult, isn't it?
I recommend boiling them.
I recommend it.
I think the dough should be good after about 10 minutes.
You're right, it's a little high.
It's coming up.
It's a bit puffy now, isn't it?
Let's start with the naan for the naan dock.
It's warm, isn't it?
You see?
If you don't keep it at this temperature, it won't stretch.
It's like talking to the dough.
Talking to it.
Only a professional can do that.
The more you do it, the more you understand
The more you do it, the more you understand how fluffy and glutinous it is.
I made a mistake once.
Try talking to him.
You're speaking out loud now.
Is it growing?
Are you okay?Are you okay?
Are you guys holding hands?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You okay?
Don't let it rip.
What's the bread saying?
He says it's gonna be okay.
We're all in this together.
Good, good, good.
All right, well, I'm gonna start taking it a little bit at a time.
He says, "I'm gonna put my fist in.
I'm gonna put my fist in, I'm gonna put my fist in.
Watch out, everybody.
You're so cute.
Watch out!
This is where it's most important that we all help each other.
Help, help, help!
This is the most important thing.
If there's no gluten...
If you don't have gluten, you'll get mumbles, mumbles...
But it's so good.
It's starting to look like naan.
Thank you, guys.
Take another one.
This time, it should be bigger.
Half this size.
Same way.
But let's make it a cheese creature.
Almost there.
So the cheese should be round?
I want the cheese round.
Here... here...
Cheese.
Let's try them all.Let's take a look at all of them!
It's pretty full.
I hope it's okay.
And here...
We'll wrap it up in a doughnut.
Like a steamed bun.
Keep pulling it in closer and closer.
This hand should be a little bit closer to the center.
Like this.
Put it on like this
Like a drawstring.
Wow, that's hard!
Squeeze it together.
Are you okay?
Put the cheese in.
Put it in.
Squeeze it in.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
Put it in.
It's okay.
Then just squeeze her.
Squeeze.
Oh! He's gone.
Yes, he's gone.
Chitty-chitty!
He's gone, isn't he?
Here's the match.
Now we're ready to bake the dough.
Here's Mr. Miyao's point... don't put oil in the pan and cover it with a lid.
I didn't expect that.
If you put oil in the pan, it's not deep frying.
When baking in a frying pan, you should never put oil on a bucket or anything like that.
You're right, that's true.
It doesn't get crispy, so if you want to make it moist, you can put oil in it.It doesn't get crispy, so if you want to bake it moist, you can put it in.
But it doesn't give off the aroma of flour.
It's like a doughnut.
It's like deep-fried bread.
This way.
Off you go!
It's already stopped puffing up.
Then it looks like it's already baked.
Is it okay?
Pop!
Just pop it.
Ready?
Poof!
Oh, it's burnt... it's burnt...
Here's a snack.
But it's okay.
It's okay, it's okay.
There's cheese in the middle.
Actually, you don't have to cook it so hard.
It's okay if it's not so well browned.
I'm afraid I'll burn it again.
What should I do?
It's so beautiful!
Looks delicious.
Thank you very much.
Looks so delicious!
so fluffy
Amazing!
I'm so happy
A bundle of happiness
Can it be a little lower?
Yes, sir
Here we go!
Wow, it's you.
It's beautiful.
You can return it when you feel it's fully inflated.I think you can return it when you think it's all puffed up.
Wow!
It looks so delicious!
It's so beautiful.
I think I'll put it in.
Here we go.
Ready?
Ta-da!
Wow.
Yeah, it's in.
Oh, wow.
Looks delicious.
I like it.
Let's finish it up.
Let's wrap it up.
I think it's fine as it is.
It's cool, isn't it?
It's big.
Drama.
Mr. Graff.
I think it's okay to crawl.
The rest is already to your liking.
Wrap it up
Pull it this way.
That's good.
Meri-meri-meri-meri, on purpose.
Yes, yes...
How's that?
Oh, please.
It's done!
The naandook and cheese kulcha are ready!
Looks delicious!
Wow...what do you think? What do you think?
At first, they were all shattered and not sticking together at all, but now they are talking to each other a lot,
They turned out so delicious and smelled so good,It turned out so delicious and smelled so good,
I am very happy.
I worked really hard on it.
Then, please try it right away.
Yes, please try it.
Start with the naandok.
Then, I'll have some.
Delicious, delicious, delicious.
I'm so glad. It's really sticky.
How do you know? We ate a lot of it together, but you know what I mean?
It was so moist and buttery.
It soaked up all the flavor.
It's so good! I'm so happy!
Let's try some of the season's kurucha.
Can we? You want some?
Okay.
Ho!
Oh!
Oh, my God! He's eating!
Yeah! Yeah! That's great!
That's so Beyonce!
It's so beyonce!
Yay!
Bon appétit! Yay! I'm so happy!
It's growing, growing, growing!
Wow! Absolutely delicious!
I'm so happy!
It's so good!
Thank goodness!
So much cheese!
My mouth is full!
On the other hand, isn't it amazing?
I can see the cheese is tender!
That's good!
Yummy! Much better!Delicious! Delicious all the time!
My mouth is already too happy!
Well, that was fun!
How was it for you?
It was almost my first time making anything.
I hadn't made bread since I was very little.
I was so nervous!
I was afraid I wouldn't be able to do it.
But it was so delicious and it looked so good.
And the taste was perfect too!
I hope you will give it another try.
If you are interested in any of the dishes, please come to Hello Kitchen again!
Please come to Hello Kitchen again!
Thank you again!
That's all for Hello Kitchen!
It's amazing.
It's delicious.
I thought the name of the dish was something I hadn't heard much about,
It looks really nice.
I recently tried making bread at home for the first time.
It looks amazing. It looks difficult.
It's called Ishida's bread, and they were allowed to sell it at the Hina Fest,
Basically, my mother is good at making bread,
I would sometimes help her out with that.
But for the first time, I wanted to bake pokacha by myself,
So I tried it,
How was it?
It was like, "Oh, I don't know, it's not like this.
I didn't feel like I had done it so well.
I usually watch my mother's baking.
I wondered if it would be like this if I made it myself.
It's not that it's not tasty.
So I was inspired by the current video,
So the current video has inspired me to try my best once more.
Yes, I am. I support you a lot.Yes, I am. I support you a lot.
Thank you.
Do you want to make it, Yume?
Yes, I do. I'm not that good at cooking,
Recently, I made curry.
I'm a bit embarrassed to say curry in front of Mr. Ishida, but...
That's nice. Because it's free. Curry is free.
I made it quickly and ate it, mixing it with a regular store-bought roux.
But next time, I would like to make it with shrimp or octopus.
That sounds good. It's good.
I think Japanese soup stock goes well with seafood,
Japanese style?
Yes, I think so.
Should I make it shabbier?
It's up to you, but maybe a little Japanese broth would change it.
Thank you very much. I will definitely make Japanese soup stock.
By all means.
Hallo! Sta.
Next is the presentation of the lyrics that touched my heart.
Project has many songs,
Project has many songs, do you have any lyrics of this song in your opinion?
Yes, I do. Juice-Juice recently released a new song,
Aoi Yamazaki wrote the lyrics for the second song, "Pride Bright".
The lyrics of the A melody is "Tokimeki Hitori Waiboke (Waiting alone for a crush)",
This song is very strong,
I'm not going to break my pride! The song is about a woman who is very strong, and her pride is unbreakable,
The image of a strong woman is often associated with this song,
I thought this word was very pure,
At first glance, she seems like a cool person,
I think it's a glimpse into the heart of a young girl,
I really like the fact that you can catch a glimpse of that part of her,
I hope you will pay attention to it and listen to it.
Do you have any comments, Mr. Ishida?
I have a new album coming out on August 30,
Chocotto Love is in it again,
It will be sung by Mei Yamazaki, Homaki Okamura, and Rio Sakurai,The three of us, Mei Yamazaki, Homare Okamura, and Rio Sakurai, sang it together,
When I heard the three of them singing the song again, I thought, "When I think of the character for love, the faces of my family came to mind first,
When I listened to them singing the song again, I thought of the word "love" and thought of my family's faces first,
I think the lyrics are very cute and beautiful.
But this song is about cuddling with the person you love all the time,
But in love, family comes to mind first.
I thought, "I was talking about lovers, lovers, lovers, lovers...? I thought, "What?
I thought, "I want to make a family with my lover someday.
I could also imagine that this girl must have grown up with a lot of love,
It made me feel warm and fuzzy.
I have to listen to it. Let's keep listening to it, everyone.
I hope you will listen to it and imagine it.
Thank you very much.
Now please watch the VTR. Here you go!
A presentation of the lyrics that touched my heart.
In this corner, we will present the lyrics of some of the Hello! Project songs,
Project songs and talk about the charm of the lyrics.
Project's songs and talk about their charms. Project songs and talk about their charms.
This week, I, Natsune Nakayama, will be presenting.
Here it is.
I will be presenting a song by Aya Matsuura called "Chiyashinshi",
This is the lyrics of the chorus of the song,
Thank you, I will be my own wind someday.
Thank you for everything you gave me, thank you for everything you gave me.
I think this song is a song that expresses my gratitude to those who support me.
The lyric "thank you" appears many times in the song.
So, as you can tell from the song, the lyrics are about saying thank you.
The first line of the song, "I'm going to be the way I am," is about me struggling to become the way I am.
I love this song because it really resonates with me.
I thought that Natsumei was interpreting that "becoming the wind" in that way, and I thought that this is how Natsumei was listening to the song, so I wanted to listen to it again after hearing it again.
I thought I wanted to listen to the song again after hearing it.
Thank you" is a good word, isn't it?
I've always been able to say thank you and I'm sorry to my grandma.
I don't know, it really hits home. I think it's great.
I felt again that this is a song of gratitude, since it appeared about five times on the trip alone.
Please look forward to the next installment!Stay tuned for the next installment!
Hallo! STE
Morning Musume。 23's Ayumi Ishida and Yume Kudo of Chew Chew Chew are presenting the latest episode of "Halo! STE, presented by Ayumi Ishida of Morning Musume!
Project's 25th Anniversary New Member Audition. Project 25th Anniversary New Member Audition!
How old were you when you auditioned, Yume? Well, I auditioned when I was in the 4th or 5th grade of elementary school.
I had never danced or sung before, but at the audition, I just greeted the auditioners and also I was into a hobby of making rubber bracelets called "fan room".
I carried it in my pocket so that I could answer any questions I was asked.
If you are asked what it is, and if you have something you can take with you, it might be a good idea to carry it in your pocket.
I think he wanted to show it to the audience because he had made something good. Do you have any episodes?
I was 14 years old when I auditioned for the show, and I don't know why, but I was so confident that I would pass the audition, that I really didn't look around me.
Recently, the members were talking about their memories of the audition, like there was this girl and that girl.
I don't remember any of them, and I was thinking only about myself, but I think it's important to have confidence.
But I think it's important to have self-confidence, so even if you don't do anything and you don't have self-confidence, I think it's important to have a good mindset.
Do you have that kind of mindset? I don't know how I feel, but I'm very confident.
I don't know how I feel about it, but I'm very confident and I think it's a good idea for me to be confident that I can pass the test.
I hope that the day will come when you can work with us.
I'm looking forward to it!
Hello Project 25th Anniversary New Member Audition will be held on August 14th, 10:00 a.m. for web applications and August 14th for mail applications.
We are looking forward to receiving many applications!
WOW!
If you don't dress up, you'll be ashamed.
You don't need a reason to go out
Study as fast as you can
Don't let your grades get in the way
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
I'm not serious
I'm not serious when I've never seen you serious.
You make assumptions about me
Don't sleep far behind me
Don't be heartless.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I don't know what love is.
I don't want to tell you.
I'm not gonna tell you if I'm dead or alive in this dream.
Of course not. You have to be a child to start it.Of course, you have to be young to start.
You don't need a reason to go out
You've got to study hard, you've got to cram
I don't want to regret my grades
Ah, it's so exciting, isn't it?
I didn't sleep.
Thank you for watching
You can't start without getting dressed up
You don't need a reason to go out
I don't need a reason to go out and study
No regrets about grades
I need to get dressed up to get started
I don't need a reason to go out
Study as fast as you can
I don't want any regrets about my grades
Ah, it's exciting, isn't it?
No point in having fun if you can't have fun
We don't need a reason to get together
We may not stand out in class
But here it doesn't matter
Ah I'm so excited
Ah I want to fall in love
Ah Ah Ah Ah
I'm almost there. Fight!
Morning Musume。 23's Ayumi Ishida and Juice- Juice's Yumi Kudo are presenting "Halo! STE, presented by Ayumi Ishida of Morning Musume。
It's time to say goodbye. Here is an announcement.
Hello! Project 2023 SUMMER CITY CIRCUIT is now being held.
Morning Musume。 23 will perform at Sendai Sunplaza Hall on August 5, and Juice- Juice will perform at Shinjuku on August 6.
We are looking forward to seeing you there.
And on August 13, Morning Musume ' 23, Angelem and Juice- Juice will perform at the Rockin' Japan Festival 2023. 23, Angulum, Juice Juice, and Airi Suzuki will also perform at the Rockin Japan Festival 2023 on August 13.
Let's have fun while watching out for heat stroke so that we can present a hot stage full of excitement.
Morning Musume。 23 will release Morning Musume。 21 Best Selection THE 25th Anniversary will be released on August 30.
As I mentioned earlier, the contents are really exciting, so I am looking forward to seeing you all picking up a copy.
And Morning Musume。 23 will be going on an autumn concert tour.
This will be the last tour for Sei Fukumura, so we will only be able to present this tour with the 14 of us for one time only.
I am looking forward to seeing many people on this tour with these 14 members.So I too am looking forward to seeing many of these 14 members.
And Morning Musume。 23 has also decided to go on an autumn tour.
We are waiting for Miki Kawashima and the 11 of us, so I hope we can show you the full power of the 11 of us.
Project 25th Anniversary concert will be held on September 9 and 10 at Yoyogi National Gymnasium 1st Daibu-kan.
This will be a special 25th anniversary concert with many of our seniors performing, so I'm looking forward to it. How about you, Miki?
Yes, I'm looking forward to it. It is a dream come true for us to perform together on this stage,
I would like to do my best so that I can show you all how cool I look and make the 25th anniversary a great success. Thank you very much for your support.
Hello! Project members will appear more and more on this channel.
New videos are uploaded every Wednesday, so please subscribe to the channel.
This time, I'll be talking with Ayumi Ishida of Morning Musume。 23's Ayumi Ishida and Juice- Juice's Yumi Kudo.
Good bye.
Please subscribe to our channel.